Daniel Cannon S.

281.391.9630 Houston.TX (Willing to relocate.) <u>Emailtinkedin</u> Github

A Junior Web Developer, that has sailed around the world serving in the US Navy for six years providing fresh water through disaster relief efforts, supported operation Enduring Freedom and supported operations involving protecting nuclear weapons at sea. After military separation I pursued the entertainment industry for sound design for video and video games. While earning that degree I delivered for a food service website and operated dispatch via web application. Today I am a school bus driver looking to find a more fulfilling and challenging career as a web development.

Skills & Tools:

Web Development

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Responsive Design, Bootstrap, Handlebars, Cookies/Local Storage, React.js, C#/ASP.NET, Node.js, Express,

Security and Session Storage, User Authentication, MySQL, MongoDB

Advanced skills using the following Audio and Video editing software: Pro Tools, Logic Pro, Final Cut Pro

Work Experience:

School Bus Driver – Katy I.S.D. – Katy, TX 281.396.7560 (Supervisor: Kale McKisson) November 2016 – Present

Delivery Driver/Dispatcher –
Bringittome.com – San Diego, CA 619.821.8182 (Owner: Sherry Nep)
August 2014 – April 2016

Steam Turbine Mechanic/Nuclear Weapons Security Guard – US Navy (DD-214 upon request) April 2004 – April 2010

Education:

University of Texas-Austin Certificate in Web Development – Grad: 03/24/18

The Art Institute of California- San Diego Bachelor of Science in Audio Production – Grad: 03/24/16